export const LoveQuestions = [
  {
    question: "You are Kind",
    answer:
      "You have a heart of gold, always ready to help others without expecting anything in return.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Supportive",
    answer:
      "Whenever I face challenges, you're my unwavering support system, cheering me on every step of the way.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Humorous",
    answer:
      "Your laughter is infectious, brightening even the dullest of days.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Intelligent",
    answer:
      "You're intellectually stimulating, engaging in insightful conversations that captivate my mind.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Compassionate",
    answer:
      "Your empathy knows no bounds, making you incredibly understanding and compassionate towards everyone you encounter.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Ambitious",
    answer:
      "You're driven and ambitious, inspiring me to pursue my own goals and dreams relentlessly.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Generous",
    answer:
      "You're incredibly giving, always willing to share what you have, be it your time, resources, or love.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Optimistic",
    answer:
      "Your positive outlook on life is contagious, turning obstacles into opportunities and setbacks into lessons.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Patient",
    answer:
      "Even in the most trying times, you remain patient and composed, handling situations with grace and poise.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Loyal",
    answer:
      "You're fiercely loyal, standing by my side through thick and thin, unwavering in your commitment to our relationship.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Creative",
    answer:
      "Your imagination knows no bounds, infusing every aspect of your life with creativity and innovation.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Honest",
    answer:
      "You're honest and transparent, always speaking your mind with sincerity and integrity.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Resilient",
    answer:
      "In the face of adversity, you remain resilient, emerging stronger and more determined than ever before.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Gentle",
    answer:
      "Your gentle touch soothes my soul, reminding me of the beauty of tenderness and affection.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Independent",
    answer:
      "You're fiercely independent, carving your own path in life with confidence and self-assurance.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Respectful",
    answer:
      "You respect me for who I am, embracing my flaws and celebrating my strengths.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Adaptable",
    answer:
      "You're adaptable and flexible, navigating life's twists and turns with grace and adaptability.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Empowering",
    answer:
      "You empower me to be the best version of myself, encouraging me to chase my dreams fearlessly.",
  },
  {
    question: "You are Love",
    answer:
      "Above all, your love is unwavering and unconditional, the foundation upon which our relationship thrives and flourishes.",
  },
];
